

SIRINART SUACHAROEN

Project Engineer

ABOUT ME

Now, I am a Process Engineer of Foster Wheeler (Thailand) Ltd., a company of Wood. I have experience in creating Piping&Instrument diagram and Process flow diagram, preparing Process data sheets, working at construction site, and procurement work with foreign supplier.

I extremely self-motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally.

I enjoy solving problem in challenging work and enjoy working as a team.

CONTACT



+66911033091



sirinart.sua@gmail.com



99/35 Krungtepkreeta Rd., Sapansung, Bangkok 10250

EDUCATION

Chulalongkorn University Master degree of Science

Petrochemistry and Polymer Science

2009-2012

GPA: 3.52

Chulalongkorn University Bachelor degree of Science

Marine Science (Oceanography)

2005-2009 GPA: 3.18

SKILLS

Languages

Thai
English (TOEIC 755)
Japanese

Programing

Comos
Bluebeam
PRO/II
Inplant
Hysys

EXPERIENCE

Process Engineer

September 2019 - Present

Foster Wheeler (Thailand) Ltd.

T3 Project

Product name: Pulp

Production capacity: 90,0000 ton/year

Client name: Lenzing

Plant location: 304 industrial estate, Prachinburi, Thailand

Responsibility: Water Treatment Plant

Process Engineer

March 2013 - September 2019

TTCL Public Company Limited

Polybutylene Succinate Plant Project

Product name: Polybutylene Succinate (PBS)

Production capacity: 20,0000 ton/year

Client name: PTT MCC Biochem Company Limited

Licensor name: Mitsubishi Chemical Coporation

Plant location: Asian Industrial Estate, Rayong, Thailand

Responsibility: Cooling Tower Equipment

Petrochemical Complex in South of Vietnam Project

Product name: Linear Low Density Polyethylene (LLDPE)

Production capacity: 500,0000 ton/year

Client name: Long Son Petrochemicals Company Limited

Licensor name: Univation Technologies

Plant location : Long Son Island, Ba Ria Vung Tua, Vietnam

Responsibility: Pneumatic Conveying and Bagging System